<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<addon id="script.lazytv"
       name="LazyTV"
       version="0.9.98"
       provider-name="KodeKarnage">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0"/>
    </requires>

<extension point="xbmc.python.script"
            library="default.py">
            <provides>executable</provides>
    </extension>

    <extension point="xbmc.service" library="service.py" start="login"></extension>

    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <summary lang="af">LazyTV</summary>
        <summary lang="ca">LazyTV</summary>
        <summary lang="de">LazyTV</summary>
        <summary lang="el">LazyTV</summary>
        <summary lang="en">LazyTV</summary>
        <summary lang="en_NZ">LazyTV</summary>
        <summary lang="en_US">LazyTV</summary>
        <summary lang="es">LazyTV</summary>
        <summary lang="fr">LazyTV</summary>
        <summary lang="fr_CA">LazyTV</summary>
        <summary lang="gl">LazyTV</summary>
        <summary lang="he">LazyTV</summary>
        <summary lang="hu">LazyTV</summary>
        <summary lang="it">LazyTV</summary>
        <summary lang="lt">LazyTV</summary>
        <summary lang="nl">LazyTV</summary>
        <summary lang="no">LazyTV</summary>
        <summary lang="pl">LazyTV </summary>
        <summary lang="pt">LazyTV</summary>
        <summary lang="pt_BR">LazyTV</summary>
        <summary lang="sv">LazyTV</summary>
        <description lang="el">Έχετε μια τεράστια συλλογή από τηλεοπτικές σειρές και δεν έχετε προλάβει να παρακολουθήσετε ούτε τα μισά επεισόδια. Γιατί μοιάζει με αγγαρεία το να καθίσετε να δείτε κάτι;&#10;Το LazyTV είναι εδώ για να εξαφανίσει τέτοιου είδους διλήμματα, και να σας επιτρέψει να ηρεμήσετε και να απολαύσετε τη συλλογή σας. Με ένα κλικ μπορείτε να κάνετε ζάπινγκ μεταξύ των σειρών σας, ή να έχετε ό,τι πιθανότατα θέλετε να δείτε να εμφανίζεται σε ένα παράθυρο.&#10;Εξάλλου, γιατί να χρειάζεται να επιλέξετε κάτι συγκεκριμένο; Το μόνο σίγουρο είναι ότι θέλετε να δείτε λίγη τηλεόραση!&#10;&#10;Σε αντίθεση με τις έξυπνες λίστες αναπαραγωγής ή τα διάφορα widget, το LazyTV δεν εμφανίζει απλά το πρώτο μη προβληθέν επεισόδιο μιας τηλ. σειράς. Εμφανίζει το πρώτο μη προβληθέν επεισόδιο ΑΜΕΣΩΣ ΜΕΤΑ το τελευταίο επεισόδιο που παρακολουθήσατε. Μια μικρή, αλλά εξαιρετικά σημαντική διαφορά.&#10;&#10;Το LazyTV έχει δυο κύριες λειτουργίες:&#10;Η πρώτη δημιουργεί και εκτελεί μια λίστα αναπαραγωγής με τυχαία επιλεγμένα επεισόδια. Και όχι ό,τι κι ό,τι, αλλά τα επόμενα επεισόδια που θεωρεί ότι επιθυμείτε να παρακολουθήσετε. Έχετε, επίσης, τη δυνατότητα να ενσωματώσετε και τις ταινίες σας (προβληθείσες και μη) για πλήρες ζάπινγκ. &#10;Η δεύτερη λειτουργία συμπληρώνει ένα παράθυρο με όλα τα επόμενα διαθέσιμα επεισόδια των τηλ. σειρών σας. Με ένα κλικ μπορείτε να δείτε το μενού προβολής, άμεσα.&#10;&#10;Μπορείτε να διαμορφώσετε την εμπειρία σας σε ακόμη μεγαλύτερο βαθμό, συνδυάζοντας οποιαδήποτε από τις κύριες λειτουργίες με μια λίστα αναπ/γής προεπιλεγμένων σειρών.&#10;Κάποιες εκπομπές, όπως κινούμενα σχέδια ή διάφορα σόου, δεν είναι απαραίτητο να προβληθούν με συγκεκριμένη σειρά, γι'αυτό το LazyTV σας δίνει τη δυνατότητα να παρακολουθήσετε τέτοιου είδους εκπομπές με τυχαία σειρά επεισοδίων.&#10;&#10;Το LazyTV διαθέτει δύο ακόμα μικρές λειτουργίες που εκτείνονται πέραν του ίδιου του πρόσθετου:&#10;Η πρώτη είναι η επιλογή να ειδοποιήστε σε περίπτωση που υπάρχει μη προβληθέν επεισόδιο πριν από αυτό που ετοιμάζεστε να παρακολουθήσετε. Αυτή η λειτουργία εξαιρεί τις τηλ. σειρές που μπορούν να προβληθούν με τυχαία σειρά επεισοδίων.&#10;Η δεύτερη επιλογή αφορά την εμφάνιση ειδοποίησης μετά την προβολή ενός επεισοδίου, ότι η επόμενη σειρά είναι διαθέσιμη, και σας ρωτά αν επιθυμείτε να την παρακολουθήσετε άμεσα.&#10;&#10;&#10;Το LazyTV περιλαμβάνει μια υπηρεσία με την οποία αποθηκεύει τις πληροφορίες των επόμενων επεισοδίων, και παρακολουθεί τις αναπαραγωγές για να προλαμβάνει αλλαγές στη βάση δεδομένων. Αυτή είναι η προσπάθειά μου να κάνω το πρόσθετο πιο γρήγορο στο Raspberry Pi. Το Pi απαιτεί μια "προθέρμανση": μια πλήρη ανανέωση των δεδομένων των επεισοδίων (που γίνεται κατά την εκκίνηση και κατά την ενημέρωση συλλογής), η οποία χρειάζεται σχεδόν 30 δευτερόλεπτα για μια συλλογή περίπου 100 σειρών*. Παρ'όλα αυτά, η λίστα με τις σειρές ανοίγει κανονικά, και η τυχαία αναπαραγωγή ξεκινά σε λιγότερο από 2 δευτερόλεπτα.&#10;&#10;*Η ίδια ενημέρωση χρειάζεται μόλις 2 δευτερόλεπτα για να γίνει στο laptop μου, με επεξεργαστή i5.</description>
        <description lang="en">You have a huge library of TV shows and you havent viewed half of it. So why does it feel like such a chore to sit down and watch something?&#10;LazyTV is here to free you from your battles with indecision, instead letting you lean back and soak up content. With one click you can be channel-surfing your own library, or have what you probably want to watch pop up in a single window.&#10;Afterall, you know you want to watch TV, so why do you also have to decide what specifically to watch?&#10;&#10;Unlike a smart playlist or skin widget, LazyTV doesnt just provide the first unwatched episode of a TV show. It provides the first unwatched episode AFTER the last watched one in your library. A small, but important, distinction.&#10;&#10;LazyTV offers two main functions:&#10;The first creates and launches a randomised playlist of the TV episodes. And not just any episodes, but the next episode it thinks you would want to watch. You also have the option to blend in your movies (both the watched and the unwatched) to complete the channel-surfing experience.&#10;The second main function populates a window with the next available episode for each of your TV Shows. One click and your viewing menu is there, immediately.&#10;&#10;Combine either of the main functions with a playlist of preselected shows to customise your experience even further.&#10;Some TV shows, like cartoons or skit shows, can be viewed out of episodic order. So LazyTV gives you the ability to identify these shows and treat them differently. Those shows will be played in a random order.&#10;&#10;LazyTV also offers two minor functions that extend beyond the addon itself:&#10;The first is an option to be notified if you are about to watch an episode that has an unwatched episode before it. This function excludes the TV shows identified as able to be watched out of order.&#10;The second option posts a notification when you finish watching a TV episode telling you that the next show is available and asks if you want to view it now.&#10;&#10;&#10;LazyTV contains a service that stores the next episodes' information and monitors your player to pre-empt database changes. This is my attempt to make the addon more responsive on my Raspberry Pi. The Pi still takes a while to "warm-up"; a full refresh of the episode data (which occurs at start-up and on a library update) takes about 30 seconds for my ~100 show library*. However, the show list window opens and the random player starts in less than 2 seconds.&#10;&#10;*The same update takes 2 seconds on my laptop with its i5 processor.</description>
        <description lang="en_US">You have a huge library of TV shows and you haven't viewed half of it. So why does it feel like such a chore to sit down and watch something?&#10;LazyTV is here to free you from your battles with indecision, instead letting you lean back and soak up content. With one click you can be channel-surfing your own library, or have what you probably want to watch pop up in a single window.&#10;After all, you know you want to watch TV, so why do you also have to decide what specifically to watch?&#10;&#10;Unlike a smart playlist or skin widget, LazyTV doesn't just provide the first unwatched episode of a TV show. It provides the first unwatched episode AFTER the last watched one in your library. A small, but important, distinction.&#10;&#10;LazyTV offers two main functions:&#10;The first creates and launches a randomized playlist of the TV episodes. And not just any episodes, but the next episode it thinks you would want to watch. You also have the option to blend in your movies (both the watched and the unwatched) to complete the channel-surfing experience.&#10;The second main function populates a window with the next available episode for each of your TV Shows. One click and your viewing menu is there, immediately.&#10;&#10;Combine either of the main functions with a playlist of preselected shows to customize your experience even further.&#10;Some TV shows, like cartoons or skit shows, can be viewed out of episodic order. So LazyTV gives you the ability to identify these shows and treat them differently. Those shows will be played in a random order.&#10;&#10;LazyTV also offers two minor functions that extend beyond the addon itself:&#10;The first is an option to be notified if you are about to watch an episode that has an unwatched episode before it. This function excludes the TV shows identified as able to be watched out of order.&#10;The second option posts a notification when you finish watching a TV episode telling you that the next show is available and asks if you want to view it now.&#10;&#10;&#10;LazyTV contains a service that stores the next episodes' information and monitors your player to pre-empt database changes. This is my attempt to make the addon more responsive on my Raspberry Pi. The Pi still takes a while to "warm-up"; a full refresh of the episode data (which occurs at start-up and on a library update) takes about 30 seconds for my ~100 show library*. However, the show list window opens and the random player starts in less than 2 seconds.&#10;&#10;*The same update takes 2 seconds on my laptop with its i5 processor.</description>
        <description lang="es">Tienes una gran colección de Series de TV y no has visto ni la mitad de ellas. ¿Cómo sería sentarse y ver algo?&#10;LazyTV está aquí para liberarte de tu lucha contra la indecisión, y te va a dejar recostarte tranquilo y ver algo. Con un simple click podrás hacer zapping entre tu propia colección, o mucho mejor, te dirá que ver en una ventanita.&#10;Después de todo, sabes que sólo quieres ver la tele ¿También tienes que decidir qué quieres ver?&#10;&#10;Al contrario que una lista inteligente, o una skin, LazyTV no solo te dice el primer episodio sin ver de una serie. Te dice cuál es el siguiente episodio que tienes que ver después de lo último que viste. Es una pequeña, pero muy importante, diferencia.&#10;&#10;LazyTV ofrece dos funciones principales:&#10;La primera es crear y lanzar una lista aleatoria de episodios de tus series. Y no sólo cualquier episodio, sino el siguiente episodio que cree que quieres ver. Además, tienes la opción de meter tambien las películas (vistas o no vistas) para completar la sensación de zapping.&#10;La segunda función principal es rellenar una ventana con los siguientes episodios disponibles para cada serie de TV. Con un click y toda la información está ahí. ¡Inmediatamente!&#10;&#10;Puedes combinar ambas funciones en una lista de series preseleccionadas para adaptar mucho mejor tu experiencia.&#10;Algunas series, como los dibujos o los programas satíricos, pueden ser vistos de manera aleatoria, sin orden. LazyTV te da la opción de identificar esos programas y tratarlos de manera diferente. Estos programas se reproducirán en orden aleatorio.&#10;&#10;LazyTV también incluye dos funciones menores que aumentan la capacidad del addon:&#10;La primera es la opción de notificarte si vas a ver un episodio y esa serie tiene algún episodio anterior que no has visto. Aquí so obvian los programas sin orden estricto.&#10;La segunda te notifica cuando terminas de ver un episodio y también tienes el siguiente. Te pregunta si quieres verlo.&#10;&#10;&#10;LazyTV contiene un servicio que almacena la información de los episodios y monitoriza las reproducciones para prever cambios en la base de datos. Estos lo hago para intentar hacer el addon más ligero en mi Raspberry Pi. La Pi todavía se tira un tiempo hasta que arranca; cuando hay una actualización de la base de datos (arranque o manual) se puede tirar 30 segundos en colección de más o menos 100 series*. De todas maneras, la lista de episodios se abre y el reproductor aleatorio empieza en menos de 2 segundos.&#10;&#10;*El mismo escenario tarda 2 segundos en mi portátil con un i5.</description>
        <description lang="fr_CA">Vous avez une vidéothèque énorme de séries télé et vous n'en avez pas regardé la moitié. Alors pourquoi cela semble-t-il être une telle corvée de s’asseoir et regarder quelque chose?&#10;LazyTV est là pour vous libérer de vos batailles avec l'indécision, vous laissant plutôt vous installer confortablement et absorber du contenu. En un clic vous pouvez surfer les chaînes de votre vidéothèque ou laisser ce que vous voudriez certainement regarder se présenter à vous dans une fenêtre.&#10;Après tout, vous savez que vous voulez regarder la télé, alors pourquoi avoir aussi à décider spécifiquement quoi regarder?&#10;&#10;À la différence d'une liste de lecture intelligente ou d'un widget d'habillage, LazyTV ne vous donne pas juste le premier épisode d'une série télé. Il vous propose le premier épisode non regardé APRÈS le dernier regardé dans votre vidéothèque. Une distinction petite mais importante.&#10;&#10;LazyTV offre deux fonctions principales :&#10;La première crée et lance une liste de lecture aléatoire des épisodes télé. Et pas juste n'importe lesquels, mais ceux qu'il pense que vous voudriez regarder. Vous avez aussi l'option d'y mélanger vos films (regardés ou non) pour compléter l'expérience de surf des chaînes.&#10;La seconde fonction principale remplit une fenêtre avec le prochaine épisode de chacune de vos séries télé. Un clic et votre menu de visionnement est là, immédiatement.&#10;&#10;Combinez l'une ou l'autre des deux fonctions principales à une liste de lecture d'émissions présélectionnées pour personnaliser encore plus votre expérience.&#10;Certaines émissions télé comme les dessins animés et les sketches peuvent être regardées sans suivre l'ordre des épisodes. Alors LazyTV vous donne la possibilité d'identifier ces émissions et de les traiter différemment. Elles seront lues en ordre aléatoire.&#10;&#10;LazyTV offre aussi deux fonctions mineures qui dépassent l'addiciel lui-même :&#10;La première est une option vous alertant si vous allez regarder un épisode qui en a un autre non regardé avant. Cette fonction exclut les émissions identifiées comme pouvant être regardées dans le désordre.&#10;La seconde option indique, quand vous finissez de regarder un épisode télé, si l'épisode suivant est disponible et vous demande si vous souhaitez le regarder présentement.&#10;&#10;LazyTV comprend un service qui stocke les informations du prochain épisode et surveille votre lecteur pour anticiper les changements dans la base de données. C'est ma tentative de rendre l'addiciel plus réactif sur mon Raspberry Pi. Le Pi prend quand même du temps à « chauffer »; un rafraîchissement complet des données des épisodes (qui a lieu au démarrage et à la mise à jour de la vidéothèque) prend environ 30 secondes pour ma vidéothèque de ~100 émissions*. Cependant, la fenêtre de liste des émissions s'ouvre et le lacture aléatoire commence en moins de 2 secondes.&#10;&#10;* La même mise à jour prend 2 secondes sur mon portable avec son processeur i5</description>
        <description lang="it">Avete una vasta libreria di spettacoli televisivi e tu non ne hai visto nemmeno la metà. Ecco perché diventa complicato sedersi e guardare qualcosa ? &#10;LazyTV è qui per liberarvi dalle vostre  indecisione, e lasciarvi a godersi i contenuti . Con un clic nella vostra libreria , è possibile avere quello che probabilmente si vuole guardare con un pop-up in una finestra .&#10;Dopotutto , si sa che si desidera guardare la TV , perché si hanno delle cose preferite da guardare&#10;&#10;A differenza di una smart playlist o un widget , LazyTV non si limita a fornire il primo episodio disponibile di uno show televisivo Esso fornisce il primo episodio disponibile dopo l'ultimo guardato nella tua libreria . Una piccola, ma importante differenza &#10;&#10;LazyTV offre due funzioni principali : .&#10;la prima crea e lancia una playlist randomizzato gli episodi televisivi. E non solo tutti gli episodi , ma l'episodio successivo che si suppone si voglia vedere . Hai anche la possibilità di fondere nei vostri film (sia visti che non visti ) per completare l'esperienza .&#10;La seconda funzione principale popola una finestra con il prossimo episodio disponibile per ciascuno dei vostri programmi TV . Un clic e il vostro menu di visualizzazione è lì , subito .&#10;&#10;Combina una delle principali funzioni con una playlist di spettacoli preselezionati per personalizzare la vostra esperienza ancora di più .&#10;alcuni spettacoli televisivi , come i cartoni animati o spettacoli , possono essere visualizzati in ordine di episodio . Così LazyTV ti dà la possibilità di identificare questi spettacoli e di trattarli in modo diverso . Tali spettacoli verranno riprodotti in ordine casuale&#10;&#10;LazyTV offre anche due funzioni minori che si estendono oltre l'addon stesso : &#10;La prima è la possibilità di essere avvisati se si sta a guardare un episodio di una serie che ha episodi non visti prima .&#10;La seconda è un opzione che notifica,alla fine della visione di un Episodio TV se il prossimo spettacolo è disponibile e chiede se lo si desidera guardare.&#10;&#10;&#10;LazyTV contiene un servizio che memorizza le informazioni sulle prossime puntate . Questo è il mio tentativo di rendere l'addon più reattivo sul mio Raspberry Pi . Il Pi vuole un po di tempo in più; un aggiornamento completo dei dati di episodi ( che si verifica all'avvio e all'aggiornamento della libreria) richiede circa 30 secondi per il mia libreria con 100 spettacoli .&#10;Tuttavia la finestra con la lista degli episodi si apre è il video parte in meno di 2 secondi&#10;Lo stesso aggiornamento richiede 2 secondi sul mio portatile con l' i5 .</description>
        <description lang="lt">Turite didžiulę TV laidų bibliotekoje ir dar neperžiūrėjote jos bent pusę. Tai kodėl prisėsti ir kažką pažiūrėti atrodo kaip sunkus darbas?&#10;LazyTV yra čia, kad išlaisvintų jus nuo neapsisprendimo ir leistų jums atsilošti ir pasinerti į turinį. Vienu paspaudimu galite naršyti biblioteką kaip televizijos kanalus ar galbūt norite pamatyti viską vieninteliame ekrane.&#10;Galų gale jūs žinote, kad norite žiūrėti televiziją, tai kodėl jūs turite konkrečiai nuspręsti ką norite žiūrėti?&#10;&#10;Kitaip nei išmanusis grojaraštis ar teminės išvaizdos valdiklis, LazyTV ne tik pateikia jums pirmą neperžiūrėtą TV laidos epizodą. Jis pateikia pirmą neperžiūrėtą epizodą PO paskutinio žiūrėto iš jūsų bibliotekos. Nedidelis, bet svarbus skirtumas.&#10;&#10;LaxyTV siūlo dvi pagrindines funkcijas:&#10;Pirma yra sukurti ir paleisti atsitiktinai sumaišytą TV epizodų grojaraštį. Ir ne tik bet kokių epizodų, o kito epizodo, kurį jo nuomone jūs norite peržiūrėti. Jūs taip turite parinktį sulieti jūsų filmus (tiek žiūrėtus, tiek nežiūrėtus), kad galėtumėte juos naršyti taip, lyg naršytumėte įprastus televizijos kanalus.&#10;Antra pagrindinė funkcija užpildo langą kiekvienos TV laidos kitu galimu epizodu. Vienas paspaudimas ir jūsų peržiūros meniu paruoštas, nedelsiant.&#10;&#10;Sujunkite bet kurią iš pagrindinių funkcijų su iš anksto parinktų laidų grojaraščių ir dar labiau pritaikykite viską savo poreikiams.&#10;Kai kurios TV laidos, tokios kaip animaciniai filmai ar humoro laidos, gali būti žiūrimo ne eilės tvarka. Taigi LazyTV suteikia jums galimybę idetifikuoti šias laidas ir elgis su jomis kitaip. Šios laidos bus atkurtos atsitiktine tvarka.&#10;&#10;LazyTV taip pat siūlo dvi nedideles funkcijas, kurios išeina už paties priedo ribų.&#10;Pirma parinktis, kurią reikia paminėti, yra kai jūs norite peržiūrėti epizodą, kuris prieš jį turi neperžiūrėtą epizodą. Ši funkcija išskiria TV laidas, kurios pažymėtos kaip galimos žiūrėti ne eilės tvarka.&#10;Antra parinktis parodo pranešimą, kai baigiate žiūrėti TV epizodą, informuojantį jus, kad yra galima kita laida ir paklausia ar norite ją peržiūrėti dabar.&#10;&#10;&#10;LazyTV turi paslaugą, kuri saugo kito epizodo informaciją ir stebi jūsų grotuvą, kad užbėgtų už akių duomenų bazės pokyčiams. Tai yra bandymas padaryti, kad priedas geriau reaguotų ant mano Pasberry Pi įrenginio. Pi vis dar reikalingas laikas apšilimui; Pilnas epizodų duomenų atnaujinimas (kuris vyksta paleidimo metu ir atnaujinant biblioteką) trunka apie 30 sekundžių mano ~100 laidų bibliotekai*. Tačiau laidos langas atsidaro ir atsitiktinis atkūrimas prasideda per mažiau nei 2 sekundes.&#10;&#10;*Tas pats atnaujinimas užtrunka mažiau nei 2 sekundes mano nešiojamame kompiuteryje su i5 procesoriumi.</description>
        <description lang="nl">Je hebt een enorme bibliotheek van TV-series en je hebt nog niet de helft bekeken. Dus waarom voelt dat als een te groot karwei om te gaan zitten en iets te bekijken?&#10;LazyTV is hier om je te bevrijden van je gevecht met besluiteloosheid, in plaats daarvan, laat je achterover leunen en geniet van alle content. met één klik kunt u kanaal surfen in jouw eigen bibliotheek, of wat je waarschijnlijk wilt kijken laten verschijnen in één enkel pop-up venster&#10;immers, je weet dat je tv wilt kijken, dus waarom moet je ook beslissen naar wat je concreet wilt kijken.&#10;&#10;in tegenstelling tot een slimme afspeellijst of de skin widget, zorgt LazyTV niet alleen voor de eerste niet-bekeken aflevering van een TV-serie. het biedt ook de eerste niet-bekeken aflevering na de LAATST bekeken aflevering in jou bibliotheek. Een klein, maar belangrijk onderscheid.&#10;&#10;LazyTV biedt 2 hoofdfuncties:&#10;&#10;De eerste creëert en lanceert een gerandomiseerde afspeellijst van de tv-afleveringen. En niet zomaar een aflevering, maar de volgende aflevering die denkt dat je zo willen zien om te bekeken. je hebt ook de mogelijkheid om je te mengen in jou films (zowel de bekeken als de niet-bekeken) om de kanaal-surf ervaring te complementeren.&#10;De tweede belangrijkste functie vult een venster met de volgende beschikbare afleveringen voor elk van uw TV-series. Eén klik en uw weergavemenu is er, Gelijk.&#10;&#10;Combineer één van de belangrijkste functies met een afspeellijst van voorgeselecteerde series om uw ervaring nog verder aan te passen.&#10;&#10;sommige TV-series, zoals cartoons of sketch afleveringen, kunnen worden bekeken uit episodische volgorde. zodoende geeft Lazy-tv u de mogelijkheid om deze series te identificeren en anders te behandelen. Die shows zullen worden gespeeld in willekeurige volgorde.&#10;&#10;LazyTV biedt ook twee kleine functies die verder gaan dan de add-on zelf:&#10;De eerste is een optie om te worden geïnformeerd als u op het punt staat om een aflevering die een niet bekeken aflevering heeft voordat u de volgende aflevering bekijkt. Deze functie sluit de tv-series Geïdentificeerd als staat niet in chronologische volgorde om bekeken te worden.&#10;&#10;De tweede optie geeft een notificatie wanneer u klaar bent met het kijken naar een aflevering en je te vertellen dat de volgende aflevering beschikbaar is en vraagt of je het nu wilt bekijken.&#10;&#10;&#10;LazyTV bevat een dienst die informatie van volgende afleveringen opslaat en controleert uw speler voor uit te lopen op wijzigingen in de database. Dit is mijn poging om de add-on beter te laten inspelen op mijn Raspberry Pi. het duurt voor de PI nog een tijdje om "op te warmen," Een volledige vernieuwing van de afleveringsgegevens (die optreedt bij het opstarten en tijdens een bibliotheekupdate) dit duurt ongeveer 30 seconden voor mijn 100 afleveringenbibliotheek*. Echter, de afleveringenlijst opent en de willekeurige speler begint in minder dan 2 seconden.&#10;&#10;*Dezelfde update duurt 2 seconden op mijn laptop met een i5 processor.</description>
        <description lang="pt_BR">You have a huge library of TV shows and you havent viewed half of it. So why does it feel like such a chore to sit down and watch something?&#10;LazyTV is here to free you from your battles with indecision, instead letting you lean back and soak up content. With one click you can be channel-surfing your own library, or have what you probably want to watch pop up in a single window.&#10;Afterall, you know you want to watch TV, so why do you also have to decide what specifically to watch?&#10;&#10;Unlike a smart playlist or skin widget, LazyTV doesnt just provide the first unwatched episode of a TV show. It provides the first unwatched episode AFTER the last watched one in your library. A small, but important, distinction.&#10;&#10;LazyTV offers two main functions:&#10;The first creates and launches a randomised playlist of the TV episodes. And not just any episodes, but the next episode it thinks you would want to watch. You also have the option to blend in your movies (both the watched and the unwatched) to complete the channel-surfing experience.&#10;The second main function populates a window with the next available episode for each of your TV Shows. One click and your viewing menu is there, immediately.&#10;&#10;Combine either of the main functions with a playlist of preselected shows to customise your experience even further.&#10;Some TV shows, like cartoons or skit shows, can be viewed out of episodic order. So LazyTV gives you the ability to identify these shows and treat them differently. Those shows will be played in a random order.&#10;&#10;LazyTV also offers two minor functions that extend beyond the addon itself:&#10;The first is an option to be notified if you are about to watch an episode that has an unwatched episode before it. This function excludes the TV shows identified as able to be watched out of order.&#10;The second option posts a notification when you finish watching a TV episode telling you that the next show is available and asks if you want to view it now.&#10;&#10;&#10;LazyTV contains a service that stores the next episodes' information and monitors your player to pre-empt database changes. This is my attempt to make the addon more responsive on my Raspberry Pi. The Pi still takes a while to "warm-up"; a full refresh of the episode data (which occurs at start-up and on a library update) takes about 30 seconds for my ~100 show library*. However, the show list window opens and the random player starts in less than 2 seconds.&#10;&#10;*The same update takes 2 seconds on my laptop with its i5 processor.</description>
        <description lang="sv">Du har ett massivt bibliotek med TV-avsnitt och du har inte tittat på hälften av det. Så varför känns det så jobbigt att sätta sig ner för att titta på något?&#10;LazyTV har kommit för att befria dig från kampen mot obeslutsamhet, istället tillåts du att luta dig bakåt och suga upp innehållet. Med ett klick kan du kanalsurfa i ditt eget bibliotek eller låta det du förmodligen vill se visas i ett enda fönster.&#10;Du vet ju att du vill se på TV så varför måste du bestämma specifikt vad du skall se på?&#10;&#10;Till skillnad från en smart spellista eller ett skaltillägg, ger LazyTV dig inte bara det första icke visade avsnittet från en TV-serie. Det ger dig det första icke visade avsnittet EFTER det senast visade avsnittet i ditt bibliotek. En liten, men ack så viktig, skillnad.&#10;&#10;LazyTV erbjuder två huvudfunktioner:&#10;Den första skapar och startar en slumpmässig spellista av avsnitten. Inte bara vilka avsnitt som helst, utan det avsnitt den tror att du vill titta på. Du har också möjligheten att blanda in dina filmer (både visade och inte visade) för att komplettera kanalsurfupplevelsen. Den andra funktionen fyller ett fönster med det kommande avsnittet för varje TV-serie du har i ditt bibliotek. Ett klick och menyn finns där, omedelbart.&#10;&#10;Kombinera någon av funktionerna med en spellista av förvalda serier eller skräddarsy upplevelsen ännu mer.&#10;Vissa TV-serier, som tecknat eller sketcher, behöver inte visas i avsnittsföljd. LazyTV ger dig möjligheten att identifiera dessa program och behandla dem annorlunda. Dessa avsnitt kommer att spelas upp i slumpmässig följd.&#10;&#10;LazyTV erbjuder också två mindre funktioner som sträcker sig utanför tillägget:&#10;Den första är möjligheten att visa en notifiering om du är på väg att se ett avsnitt där du inte har tittat på det tidigare avsnittet. Funktionen inkluderar inte de TV-avsnitt som identifierats som möjliga att se i slumpmässig ordning.&#10;Den andra funktionen visar en notifiering när du slutat se på ett avsnitt med meddelandet om att nästa avsnitt finns tillgängligt och frågar om du vill se det nu.&#10;&#10;LazyTV innehåller en tjänst som lagrar de kommande avsnittens information och övervakar din spelare att föregripa databasändringar. Detta är mitt försök att göra tillägget mer responsivt på min Raspberry Pi. Raspberry Pi tar en stund att "värma upp"; en komplett uppdatering av avsnittsdata (som sker vid uppstart och biblioteksuppdatering) tar ungefär 30 sekunder för mitt bibliotek med ca 100 program*. Avsnittslistan och den slumpmässiga uppspelningen startar under två sekunder.&#10;&#10;*Samma uppdatering tar 2 sekunder på min laptop med i5 processor.</description>
        <language>en</language>
        <platform>all</platform>
        <license>GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE Version 3, 29 June 2007</license>
        <forum>http://forum.xbmc.org/showthread.php?tid=170975</forum>
        <website>http://wiki.xbmc.org/index.php?title=Add-on:LazyTV</website>
        <email>subliminal.karnage at gmail dot com</email>
        <source>https://github.com/KODeKarnage/script.lazytv/</source>
    </extension>
</addon>
