<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<addon id="script.xbmcbackup"
    name="Backup" version="1.7.1" provider-name="robweber">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.python" version="3.0.0"/>
    <import addon="script.module.dateutil" version="2.8.0" />
    <import addon="script.module.future" version="0.18.2+matrix.1" />
    <import addon="script.module.dropbox" version="10.3.1" />
    <import addon="script.module.pyqrcode" version="1.2.1+matrix.1" />
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.python.script" library="default.py">
     <provides>executable</provides>
  </extension>
  <extension point="xbmc.service" library="service.py" />
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <platform>all</platform>
    <license>MIT</license>
    <forum>https://forum.kodi.tv/showthread.php?tid=129499</forum>
    <source>https://github.com/robweber/xbmcbackup</source>
    <assets>
    	<icon>resources/images/icon.png</icon>
		<screenshot>resources/images/screenshot1.jpg</screenshot>
		<screenshot>resources/images/screenshot2.jpg</screenshot>
		<screenshot>resources/images/screenshot3.jpg</screenshot>
		<screenshot>resources/images/screenshot4.jpg</screenshot>
    </assets>
    <news>Version 1.7.1
trim spaces around Dropbox key/secret entry
fix error with zip file restores
added additional information when gathering files
</news>
    <summary lang="ar_SA">إنسخ إحتياطياً قاعده بيانات إكس بى إم سى وملفات اﻹعدادات فى حاله وقوع إنهيار مع إمكانيه اﻹسترجاع</summary>
    <summary lang="bg_BG">Добавката може да създава резервни копия и възстановява базата данни и настройките на Kodi, в случай на срив или повреда на файловете.</summary>
    <summary lang="ca_ES">Feu còpies de seguretat i restaureu la vostra base de dades de l&apos;Kodi i dels fitxers de configuració en el cas de fallada o corrupció dels fitxers.</summary>
    <summary lang="cs_CZ">Zálohování a obnovení vaší databáze Kodi a konfiguračních souborů v případě chyby nebo poškození souboru.</summary>
    <summary lang="da_DK">Sikkerhedskopiér og genskab din Kodi database og konfigurationsfiler i tilfælde af et nedbrud eller en ødelagt fil.</summary>
    <summary lang="de_DE">Die Kodi-Datenbank sichern und bei Dateiverlust oder Beschädigung wiederherstellen.</summary>
    <summary lang="el_GR">Δημιουργήστε αντίγραφα ασφαλείας της βάσης δεδομένων και των ρυθμίσεων του Kodi για την πιθανότητα σφαλμάτων ή καταστροφής αρχείων.</summary>
    <summary lang="en_GB">Backup and restore your Kodi database and configuration files in the event of a crash or file corruption.</summary>
    <summary lang="en_NZ">Backup and restore your Kodi database and configuration files in the event of a crash or file corruption.</summary>
    <summary lang="en_US">Backup and restore your Kodi database and configuration files in the event of a crash or file corruption.</summary>
    <summary lang="es_ES">Haz copia de seguridad de tu base de datos y configuración y recupera todo en caso de fallo.</summary>
    <summary lang="es_MX">Respalda y restaura tu base de datos y archivos de configuración de Kodi dado el evento de un cierre inesperado o corrupción de archivos.</summary>
    <summary lang="et_EE">Varunda ja taasta Kodi andmebaas ja seadistusfailid krahhi või failikahjustuse korral.</summary>
    <summary lang="eu_ES">Kodi datu-basea eta konfigurazio fitxategien babes-kopia egin kraskatze edo fitxategi hondamena saihesteko</summary>
    <summary lang="fi_FI">Varmuuskopioi ja palauttaa Kodin tietokannan ja asetukset kaatumisen tai tiedostojen korruptoitumisen varalta.</summary>
    <summary lang="fr_CA">Sauvegarder et restaurer votre base de données et vos fichiers de configuration Kodi dans le cas d&apos;un plantage ou d&apos;une corruption de fichier.</summary>
    <summary lang="fr_FR">Sauvegarder et restaurer les bases de données Kodi et les fichiers de configuration personnels en cas de plantage ou de fichiers corrompus.</summary>
    <summary lang="gl_ES">Crear copia de seguranza e restaurar a base de datos e ficheiros de configuración de Kodi no caso dun fallo ou corrupción de ficheiros.</summary>
    <summary lang="he_IL">גיבוי ושחזור מסד הנתונים וקבצי ההגדרות של קודי במקרה של קריסה או קבצים פגומים.</summary>
    <summary lang="hr_HR">Sigurnosno kopirajte i obnovite vašu Kodi bazu podataka i datoteke podešavanja prilikom rušenja ili oštećenja datoteka.</summary>
    <summary lang="hu_HU">Biztonsági mentés készítése az Kodi adatbázisról és a beállítófájlokról vagy állítsa helyre azokat egy rendszerösszeomlás vagy adatvesztés után.</summary>
    <summary lang="id_ID">Cadangkan dan kembalikan basis data Kodi Anda beserta berkas konfigurasi apabila terjadi kerusakan atau korupsi berkas.</summary>
    <summary lang="it_IT">Effettua il backup o ripristina il tuo database di Kodi e i file di configurazione qualora si verifichi una chiusura imprevista o un danneggiamento dei file.</summary>
    <summary lang="ja_JP">システムのクラッシュやファイル破損に備えて、Kodi のデータベースや設定ファイルをバックアップ・リストアできます。</summary>
    <summary lang="ko_KR">Kodi 데이터베이스와 설정 파일을 백업하고 복구합니다.</summary>
    <summary lang="lt_LT">Sukurkite savo Kodi duomenų bazės ir konfigūracijos failų atsarginę kopiją ir atstatykite iš jos, jei sistema užstrigtų ar susigadintų failas.</summary>
    <summary lang="nb_NO">Sikkerhetskopier og gjenopprett dine Kodi-databaser og -konfigurasjonsfiler i tilfelle et krasj eller filkorrupsjon.</summary>
    <summary lang="nl_NL">Backup en herstel je Kodi database- en configuratiebestanden in geval van een crash of bestandscorruptie.</summary>
    <summary lang="pl_PL">Tworzenie i przywracanie kopii zapasowej bazy danych i konfiguracji Kodi, na wypadek awarii lub uszkodzenia pliku.</summary>
    <summary lang="pt_BR">Faça backup e restaure o banco de dados do Kodi e seus arquivos de configuração, no caso de falha ou corrupção de arquivo.</summary>
    <summary lang="pt_PT">Crie cópias de segurança da base de dados do Kodi e dos ficheiros de configuração. Pode restaurar o conteúdo se ocorrer um crash ou corrupção de ficheiros.</summary>
    <summary lang="ru_RU">Сохраняйте и восстанавливайте базу данных и конфигурационные файлы Kodi, чтобы не допустить потерю данных в случае аварии или повреждений файлов.</summary>
    <summary lang="sk_SK">Zálohovanie a obnova Kodi databázy a konfiguračných súborov pre prípad havárie alebo poškodenia súboru.</summary>
    <summary lang="sl_SI">Varnostno kopirajte in obnovite svojo zbirko podatkov Kodi in prilagoditvene datoteke za primer sesutja ali okvare datotek.</summary>
    <summary lang="sv_SE">Ta backupp av eller återställ din Kodi-databas och konfigurationsfiler i händelse av en krash eller filkorruption.</summary>
    <summary lang="zh_CN">备份和恢复 Kodi 数据库和配置文件，以防范系统崩溃或文件损坏问题。</summary>
    <description lang="ar_SA">أسبق لك ان أضعت تخصيصاتك المفضله ورغبت لو كان بإمكانك نسخهم إحتياطياً ؟ اﻷن بات بإمكانك ذلك. يمكنك إستخراج قاعده بياناتك وقوائم التشغيل والملحقات وتخصيصاتك المفضله وغيره الى اى مصدر خارجى قابل للكتابه من قِبَل إكس بى إم سى او مباشرتاً الى نظام تخزين سحابى. يمكنك تفعيل النسخ اﻹحتياطى عند الحاجه او جدولته مُسبقاً</description>
    <description lang="bg_BG">Да сте губили всички настройки, които сте правили по Kodi? А разполагахте ли с резервно копие? Сега можете да създавате копие само с едно кликване - на базата данни, плейлистите, миниатюрите, добавките и други, в определено от вас място или директно в Dropbox. Можете да настроите и автоматично създаване на копия през определен интервал от време.</description>
    <description lang="ca_ES">Alguna vegada s&apos;ha carregat la seva configuració de l&apos;Kodi i ha desitjat tenir una còpia de seguretat? Ara pot fer-ho amb un simple clic. Pot exportar la seva base de dades, llista de reproducció, miniatures, complements i altres detalls de la configuració a qualsevol font que pugui ser escrita per l&apos;Kodi o directament a l&apos;emmagatzematge en el núvol Dropbox. Les còpies de seguretat es poden executar sota demanda o per mitjà d&apos;un planificador.</description>
    <description lang="cs_CZ">Pokazila se vám někdy konfigurace Kodi a přáli jste si, abyste měli zálohu? Nyní ji můžete mít pomocí jednoho jednoduchého kliknutí. Můžete exportovat svou databázi, seznam stop, náhledy, doplňky a další konfigurace do jakéhokoliv zdroje, do kterého může Kodi zapisovat, nebo přímo do cloudového úložiště Dropbox. Zálohy mohou být spuštěny na vyžádání nebo prostřednictvím plánovače.</description>
    <description lang="da_DK">Har du prøvet at slette din Kodi opsætning, og ønsket at du havde haft sikkerhedskopi? Nu kan du få det med et enkelt klik. Du kan eksportere din database, playlister, miniaturebilleder, add-ons og andre opsætningsdetaljer til enhver kilde, som er skrivbar for Kodi eller direkte til Dropbox cloud lager. Sikkerhedskopier kan køres manuelt eller via en tidsplan. </description>
    <description lang="de_DE">Wurde jemals deine Kodi-Konfiguration zerschossen und hättest dir dann gewünscht, dass eine Datensicherung existiert? Jetzt kannst du eine Sicherung mit nur einem Klick erzeugen. Du kannst deine Datenbanken, Wiedergabelisten, Vorschaubilder, Addons und andere Konfigurationsdetails an einem für Kodi beschreibbaren Ort deiner Wahl oder direkt in den Dropbox Cloud-Speicher exportieren. Datensicherungen können auf Anfrage oder durch ein Steuerprogramm ausgeführt werden. </description>
    <description lang="el_GR">Σας έτυχε ποτέ να χάσετε τις ρυθμίσεις του Kodi και να εύχεστε να είχατε αντίγραφο ασφαλείας; Πλέον μπορείτε με ένα απλό κλικ. Μπορείτε να εξάγετε τη βάση δεδομένων, τις λίστες αναπαραγωγής, τις μικρογραφίες, τα πρόσθετα και άλλες λεπτομέρειες της εγκατάστασης σε οποιαδήποτε πηγή στην οποία μπορεί να γράψει το Kodi, ή απευθείας στο λογαριασμό σας στο Dropbox. Τα αντίγραφα μπορούν να γίνονται κατ&apos; επιλογή ή μέσω προγραμματισμού.</description>
    <description lang="en_GB">Ever hosed your Kodi configuration and wished you&apos;d had a backup? Now you can with one easy click. You can export your database, playlist, thumbnails, addons and other configuration details to any source writeable by Kodi or directly to Dropbox cloud storage. Backups can be run on demand or via a scheduler. </description>
    <description lang="en_NZ">Ever hosed your Kodi configuration and wished you&apos;d had a backup? Now you can with one easy click. You can export your database, playlist, thumbnails, addons and other configuration details to any source writeable by Kodi or directly to Dropbox cloud storage. Backups can be run on demand or via a scheduler. </description>
    <description lang="en_US">Ever hosed your Kodi configuration and wished you&apos;d had a backup? Now you can with one easy click. You can export your database, playlist, thumbnails, addons and other configuration details to any source writeable by Kodi or directly to Dropbox cloud storage. Backups can be run on demand or via a scheduler. </description>
    <description lang="es_ES">¿Alguna vez te has cargado la configuración de Kodi y habrías deseado tener una copia de seguridad? Ahora puedes tenerla con un único click. Exporta tus base de datos, listas de reproducción, miniaturas, addons y resto de configuraciones a cualquier fuente accesible por Kodi o a tu almacenamiento en Dropbox. Las copias de seguridad pueden programarse o realizarse bajo demanda.</description>
    <description lang="es_MX">¿Alguna vez has arruinado tu configuración de Kodi y has deseado tener un respaldo? Ahora puedes tenerlo con un simple clic. Puedes exportar tu base de datos, listas de reproducción, miniaturas, comlpementos y otras configuraciones en cualquier lugar donde Kodi tenga acceso de escritura. Los respaldos pueden ser efectuados manualmente o acorde a una programación. </description>
    <description lang="et_EE">Kas oled vahel seadistanud Kodi ja soovinud, et oleks varukoopia? Nüüd saab seda teha ühe lihtsa klõpsuga. Võimalik on eksportida oma andmebaasi, esitusloendeid, pisipilte, lisamooduleid ja muid seadistuse üksikasju mis tahes Kodi poolt kirjutatavasse allikasse või otse Dropbox pilve. Varukoopiaid saab luua käsitsi või ajakava abil. </description>
    <description lang="fi_FI">Oletko joskus hukannut Kodin asetukset ja harmitellut varmuuskopioiden puutetta? Nyt voit varmuuskopioida asetuksesi napin painalluksella. Voit tallentaa tietokantasi, toistolistasi, kuvasi, lisäosasi ja muut tiedot mihin tahansa paikkaan, johon Kodilla on kirjoitusoikeudet. Lisäosa tukee myös varnuuskopiointia Dropboxiin. Varmuuskopiointi voidaan suorittaa tarvittaessa tai tietyllä aikataululla. </description>
    <description lang="fr_CA">Avez-vous déjà ruiné votre configuration Kodi et souhaité avoir une sauvegarde? Vous le pouvez maintenant en un seul clic. Vous pouvez exporter vos base de données, liste de lecture, imagettes, addiciels et autres détails de configurations vers n&apos;importe quelle source inscriptible depuis Kodi ou directement vers le stockage en nuage Dropbox. Les sauvegardes peuvent être exécutées sur demande ou à l&apos;aide d&apos;un ordonnanceur.</description>
    <description lang="fr_FR">Déjà perdu une configuration Kodi et espéré avoir fait une sauvegarde avant ? Maintenant, il est permis de le faire en un simple clic. Il est possible d&apos;exporter les bases de données, listes de lecture, miniatures, extensions et autres fichiers de configuration vers n&apos;importe quel endroit accessible depuis Kodi. </description>
    <description lang="gl_ES">De seguro que algunha vez eliminou a configuración do Kodi e desexou ter unha copia de seguranza?. Agora pode cun só clic. Pode exportar a súa base de datos, listaxes de reprodución, miniaturas, complementos e outros detalles da configuración a calquera medio escribíbel ou directamente ao Dropbox. As copias de seguranza pódense executar baixo demanda ou programadas.</description>
    <description lang="he_IL">האם אי פעם נפגמו הגדרות קודי וייחלת שהיה לך גיבוי ? כעת אתה יכול ליצור כזה בלחיצת כפתור. ניתן לייצא את בסיס הנתונים, רשימות ההשמעה, התמונות הממוזערות, הרחבות והגדרות נוספות לכל יעד שיש לקודי הרשאת כתיבה לו או ישירות לשירות אחסון הענן דרופבוקס. ניתן לתזמן מראש גיבויים או להריצם ידנית.</description>
    <description lang="hr_HR">Jeste li ikada oštetili vaša Kodi podešavanja i poželjeli ste ih obnoviti iz sigurnosne kopije? Sada to možete jednim klikom. Možete izvesti vašu bazu podataka, popis izvođenja, minijature, dodatke i ostale pojedinosti podešavanja na svaki izvor dostupan Kodiju ili izravno na Dropbox oblak pohrane. Sigurnosno kopiranje se može pokrenuti na zahtjev ili u planiranom vremenu.</description>
    <description lang="hu_HU">Sikerült már összekutyulni az Kodi beállításait és jó lett volna egy biztonsági mentés? Most megteheti egy kattintással. Exportálhatja az adatbázisait, lejátszáslistáit, könyvjelzőit, kiegészítőit és egyéb beállításokat bármely, az Kodi által írható tárhelyre vagy közvetlenül a Dropbox felhő tárolóba. A mentések kézzel vagy időzítetten indíthatóak.</description>
    <description lang="id_ID">Pernah membuat berantakan konfigurasi Kodi Anda dan berharap Anda punya cadangannya? Sekarang Anda dapat melakukannya dengan klik mudah. Anda dapat mengekspor basis data, daftar putar, gambar kecil, addon dan rincian konfigurasi lainnya ke sumber mana saja yang dapat ditulis oleh Kodi atau langsung ke penyimpanan awan Dropbox. Pencadangan dapat dijalankan sesuai permintaan atau terjadwal.</description>
    <description lang="it_IT">Hai mai distrutto la tua configurazione di Kodi ma non ne avevi una copia di backup? Ora puoi farlo con un semplice click. Puoi esportare il tuo database, le playlist, le anteprime, gli add-on ed altre configurazioni su ogni percorso accessibile da Kodi o direttamente su Dropbox. I backup si possono fare a richiesta o possono essere pianificati.</description>
    <description lang="ja_JP">Kodiの設定が消えてしまい、バックアップをとっておけば... と思ったことはありますか？これからは1クリックで簡単にバックアップできます。データベース、プレイリスト、サムネール、アドオン、その他設定項目を、Kodi が書き込み可能なメディアに書き出せます。Dropbox クラウドストレージにも直接書き出せます。スケジューラによる自動バックアップと、オンデマンドでのバックアップの両方が使えます。</description>
    <description lang="ko_KR">Kodi 설정 백업본이 있었으면 하고 원했던 적이 있습니까? 이제 한 번의 클릭으로 가능합니다. 데이터베이스, 재생목록, 썸네일, 애드온과 기타 세부 설정을 어디에나 내보내거나 직접 Dropbox 에 저장할 수 있습니다. 백업은 수동 또는 예약으로 실행할 수 있습니다. </description>
    <description lang="lt_LT">Ar kada nors praradote savo Kodi konfigūraciją ir gailėjotės, kad neturėjote atsarginės kopijos? Dabar galite ją turėti vienu paspaudimu. Jūs galite išeksportuoti duomenų bazę, grojaraščius, priedus ir kitą konfigūracijos informaciją į bet kokį Kodi palaikomą šaltinį ar tiesiai į Dropbox debesų saugyklą. Atsarginės kopijos gali būti daromos rankiniu arba automatiniu būdu.</description>
    <description lang="nb_NO">Har du noen gang ødelagt Kodi-installasjonen din og ønsket at du hadde en sikkerhetskopi? Det kan du nå med et enkelt trykk. Du kan eksportere din database, spillelister, miniatyrer, utvidelser og andre konfigurasjonsdetaljer til enhver kilde som er tilgjengelig for Kodi eller til Dropbox. Du kan lage sikkerhetskopier ved behov eller med en timeplan.</description>
    <description lang="nl_NL">Ooit je Kodi-configuratie verknald en hoopte je dat je een backup had? Nu kan dat met een simpele klik. Je kunt je bibliotheek, afspeellijsten, miniaturen, addons en andere configuratie-opties naar elke bron die door Kodi beschrijfbaar is of direct naar een Dropbox-cloudopslag exporteren. Backups kunnen op aanvraag of via planning gemaakt worden.</description>
    <description lang="pl_PL">Doświadczyłeś utraty konfiguracji Kodi i marzyłeś o posiadaniu kopii zapasowej? Teraz możesz ją mieć i to w prosty sposób. Możesz wyeksportować bazę danych, listy odtwarzania, miniatury, dodatki oraz pozostałe pliki do dowolnego źródła, włączając w to Dropbox, bezpośrednio z Kodi. Kopie zapasowe mogą zostać utworzone na żądanie lub wg harmonogramu.</description>
    <description lang="pt_BR">Sempre se preocupou com sua configuração do Kodi e desejou ter um backup? Agora você pode com um simples clique. Você pode exportar seu banco de dados, listas de reprodução, miniaturas, addons e outros detalhes de configuração para qualquer fonte gravável pelo Kodi ou diretamente ao armazenamento na nuvem Dropbox. Os backups podem ser executados sob demanda ou por agendamento.</description>
    <description lang="pt_PT">Já arruinou a sua configuração do Kodi e desejou ter feito uma cópia de segurança? Agora pode, com apenas um clique. Exporte a base de dados, listas de reprodução, miniaturas, add-ons e outras configurações para qualquer fonte acedível pelo Kodi. As cópias de segurança podem ser executadas manualmente ou por temporizador.</description>
    <description lang="ru_RU">Хотите получить резервную копию настроек Kodi? Теперь можете это сделать одним щелчком мыши. Вы можете выгрузить вашу базу данных, плейлисты, эскизы, дополнения и другую нужную Вам информацию и сохранить её с помощью Kodi или выгрузить в облачное хранилище Dropbox. Резервную копию можно сделать по требованию или запускать по расписанию. </description>
    <description lang="sk_SK">Už ste niekedy poškodili konfiguráciu Kodi a priali si mať zálohu? Teraz môžete - na jeden klik. Môžete exportovať Vašu databázu, playlist, náhľady, doplnky a konfigurácie na ktorýkoľvek zdroj zapisovateľný Kodi. Zálohy môžu byť púšťané na požiadanie alebo plánovačom. </description>
    <description lang="sv_SE">Har du någonsin tappat bort din Kodi konfiguration och önskat att du hade en backup? Nu kan du enkelt med ett klick. Du kan exportera din databas, spellista, minityrer, tillägg och andra konfigurationsdetaljer till valfri källa som är skrivbar för Kodi. Backupper kan köras på begäran eller via scheman.</description>
    <description lang="zh_CN">你是否经常折腾你的 Kodi，因而希望能够有个备份？现在可以通过简单点击来实现。你可以把资料库、播放列表、缩略图、插件和其他配置细节导出到 Kodi 可以写入的任意位置或 Dropgox 云存储空间。备份可以按需运行或通过计划任务执行。 </description>
  </extension>
</addon>
