<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<addon id="script.cinemavision" name="CinemaVision" version="1.1.1" provider-name="CinemaVision">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.14.0"/>
        <import addon="script.module.youtube.dl" version="15.318.0"/>
        <import addon="script.module.beautifulsoup" version="3.0.8"/>
        <import addon="script.module.requests" version="2.3.0"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.script" library="addon.py">
        <provides>executable</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <summary lang="en">Create a movie theater experience in the comfort of your own home!</summary>
        <summary lang="fr">Créez une expérience de cinéma dans le confort de votre maison!</summary>
        <summary lang="es">Crear una experiencia de cine en la comodidad de su propia casa!</summary>
        <summary lang="de">Erstellen Sie ein Kinoerlebnis in den Komfort der Ihren eigenen vier Wänden!</summary>
        <summary lang="pt_BR">Crie uma experiência de cinema no conforto da sua própria casa!</summary>
        <description lang="en">Create a completely customizable sequence of trivia slides, video bumpers, trailers and much more that will bring the experience of a movie theater straight to your home theater. Easily control your RESTful home automation solutions to create your perfect theater ambiance. Share your sequences, download content and collaborate online at CinemaVision.tv!</description>
        <description lang="fr">Créez une séquence complètement personnalisable de diapositives, de pare-chocs vidéo, de bandes-annonces et bien d'autres choses qui apporteront l'expérience d'un cinéma directement à votre home cinéma. Contrôlez facilement vos solutions de domotique RESTful pour créer votre ambiance de théâtre parfaite. Partagez vos séquences, téléchargez le contenu et collaborez en ligne sur CinemaVision.tv!</description>
        <description lang="es">Cree una secuencia completamente personalizable de diapositivas trivia, parachoques de video, trailers y mucho más que traerá la experiencia de un cine directamente a su cine en casa. Controle fácilmente sus soluciones RESTful de automatización del hogar para crear su ambiente de teatro perfecto. Comparte tus secuencias, descarga contenido y colabora online en CinemaVision.tv!</description>
        <description lang="de">Erstellen Sie eine vollständig anpassbare Sequenz von Trivia-Folien, Video-Stoßfänger, Trailer und vieles mehr, die die Erfahrung eines Kino direkt zu Ihrem Heimkino bringen wird. Einfache Kontrolle Ihrer RESTful Hausautomation Lösungen, um Ihre perfekte Theater Ambiente zu schaffen. Teilen Sie Ihre Sequenzen, laden Sie Inhalte herunter und arbeiten Sie online bei CinemaVision.tv zusammen!</description>
        <description lang="pt_BR">Crie uma seqüência completamente customizável de slides de trivia, amortecedores de vídeo, trailers e muito mais que trará a experiência de um cinema diretamente para seu home theater. Controle facilmente suas soluções de automação residencial RESTful para criar seu ambiente de teatro perfeito. Compartilhe suas seqüências, baixe conteúdo e colabore online no CinemaVision.tv!</description>
        <disclaimer lang="en">This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-ShareAlike 4.0 International License. Visit the website for details.</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="fr">Ce travail est autorisé sous licence Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-ShareAlike 4.0 International License. Visitez le site pour plus de détails.</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="es">Esta obra está bajo una licencia internacional Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-ShareAlike 4.0. Visite el sitio web para más detalles.</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="de">Diese Seite ist unter einer Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-ShareAlike 4.0 Internationale lizensiert. Besuchen Sie die Website für weitere Details.</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="pt_BR">Esta obra está licenciada sob uma Licença Internacional Creative Commons Attribution-Noncommercial-Share Alike 4.0. Visite o site para mais detalhes.</disclaimer>
        <platform>all</platform>
        <license>Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-ShareAlike 4.0 International</license>
        <forum>https://cinemavision.tv/forums</forum>
        <website>https://cinemavision.tv/</website>
        <source>https://github.com/CinemaVision/script.cinemavision</source>
        <assets>
            <icon>icon.png</icon>
            <screenshot>resources/screenshots/screenshot00.png</screenshot>
            <screenshot>resources/screenshots/screenshot01.png</screenshot>
            <screenshot>resources/screenshots/screenshot02.png</screenshot>
        </assets>
        <news>change: Enhanced user interface
add: Ability to change interface theme
add: TMDB trailer scraper
fix: Compatibility fixes for Kodi v18
add: Actions: Added ID to http requests to help match request to response
add: Actions: Improve sleep:// handling
add: Actions: Improve testing
change: Actions: python:// is now used for inline python statements, script:// for executing a python file
add: Trailers: Content scraper will now read genre and rating from .nfo files
add: Support for special:// content paths - Issue #124
        </news>
    </extension>
</addon>
