<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<addon id="screensaver.isslive" name="Earth View Live in HD Screensaver" version="1.0.0" provider-name="Lunatixz">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.25.0"/>
        <import addon="script.module.beautifulsoup4" version="4.3.2"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.ui.screensaver" library="default.py"/>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.script"  library="default.py"/>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <summary lang="en_GB">The High Definition Earth Viewing (HDEV) experiment aboard the ISS was activated April 30, 2014. It is mounted on the External Payload Facility of the European Space Agency’s Columbus module. This experiment includes several commercial HD video cameras aimed at the earth which are enclosed in a pressurized and temperature controlled housing. Video from these cameras is transmitted back to earth and also streamed live on this channel. While the experiment is operational, views will typically sequence though the different cameras. Between camera switches, a gray and then black color slate will briefly appear. Since the ISS is in darkness during part of each orbit, the images will be dark at those times. During periods of loss of signal with the ground or when HDEV is not operating, a gray color slate or previously recorded video may be seen.[CR]QUICK NOTES ABOUT HDEV VIDEO:[CR]- Black Image = International Space Station (ISS) is on the night side of the Earth.[CR]- No Audio = Normal. There is no audio by design.</summary>
        <description lang="en_GB"></description>
        <license>GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE. Version 3, June 2007</license>
        <platform>all</platform>
        <source>https://github.com/Lunatixz/XBMC_Addons/tree/master/screensaver.isslive</source>
        <disclaimer lang="en_GB" >- Not recommend for metered Internet[CR]- Live feeds may become inactive, this screensaver is not recommend for long-term absent use.</disclaimer>  
        <news></news>
        <assets>
            <icon>resources/images/icon.png</icon>
            <fanart>resources/images/fanart.jpg</fanart>
            <screenshot>resources/images/screenshot01.png</screenshot>
            <screenshot>resources/images/screenshot02.png</screenshot>
            <screenshot>resources/images/screenshot03.png</screenshot>
        </assets>
    </extension>
</addon>
