<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<addon id="screensaver.digitalclock"
	name="Digital Clock Screensaver"
	version="6.0.4"
	provider-name="Vojislav Vlasic">
	<requires>
		<import addon="xbmc.python" version="3.0.0"/>
		<import addon="script.skin.helper.colorpicker" version="1.0.1"/>
	</requires>
	<extension point="xbmc.ui.screensaver" library="default.py"/>
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<platform>all</platform>
		<license>GPL-2.0-or-later</license>
		<forum>https://forum.kodi.tv/showthread.php?tid=237338</forum>
		<source>https://github.com/vdb86/screensaver.digitalclock</source>
		<news>
			6.0.4 (2023-8-16) - Translations and a visual improvement for ftv skin - thanks Kevin!
			6.0.3 (2021-9-7) - Bug fixes and translations
			6.0.2 (2021-1-20) - Got skin.helper.backgrounds to work again
			6.0.1 (2021-1-15) - Added support for several skins and fixed a bug
			6.0.0 (2020-12-30) - Updated the screensaver to work with Kodi 19, fixed settings quite a bit, added options: no padding for hours, dim for the background, combine song artist and title, show only music information and RSS
		</news>
		<assets>
			<icon>resources/icon.png</icon>
			<fanart>resources/fanart.png</fanart>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-1.png</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-2.png</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-3.png</screenshot>
		</assets>
		<summary lang="da_DK">Pauseskærm med digitalt ur</summary>
		<summary lang="de_DE">Bildschirmschoner Digitaluhr</summary>
		<summary lang="en_GB">Digital clock screensaver</summary>
		<summary lang="es_ES">Salvapantallas Reloj digital</summary>
		<summary lang="it_IT">Salvaschermo orologio digitale</summary>
		<summary lang="pl_PL">Wygaszacz ekranu jako zegar cyfrowy</summary>
		<summary lang="ru_RU">Застава &quot;Цифровые часы&quot;</summary>
		<summary lang="sr_RS@latin">Čuvar ekrana digitalni sat</summary>
		<summary lang="zh_CN">数字时钟屏幕保护程序</summary>
		<description lang="da_DK">Pauseskærm med digitalt ur og dato, afspilningsinformation, vejrinformation, billeddiasshow og flere indstillinger.</description>
		<description lang="de_DE">Bildschirmschoner mit Digitaluhr, Datum, Information über die aktuelle Wiedergabe, Wetter, Diashow und weitere Optionen.</description>
		<description lang="en_GB">Digital clock screensaver with date, now playing information, weather information, image slideshow and several options.</description>
		<description lang="en_NZ">Digital clock screensaver with date, now playing information, weather information, image slideshow and several options.</description>
		<description lang="es_ES">Salvapantallas de reloj digital con fecha, información de reproducción actual, información meteorológica, presentación de imágenes y varias opciones.</description>
		<description lang="fr_CA">Économiseur d&apos;écran affichant une horloge numérique avec la date, des informations sur la lecture en cours, la météo, un diaporama d&apos;images et plusieurs options.</description>
		<description lang="fr_FR">Économiseur d&apos;écran horloge numérique avec date, informations de lecture, informations météo, avec diaporama d&apos;images et plusieurs options.</description>
		<description lang="it_IT">Salvaschermo orologio digitale con data, informazioni su elementi in riproduzione, meteo, presentazione immagini e altre opzioni.</description>
		<description lang="lt_LT">Skaitmeninio laikrodžio ekrano užsklanda su data, šiuo metu atkuriamo įrašo bei orų informacija, skaidrių demonstracija ar keletu kitų parinkčių</description>
		<description lang="ms_MY">Penyelamat skrin jam digital dengan tarikh, maklumat kini dimainkan, maklumat cuaca, paparan slaid imej dan beberapa pilihan lain.</description>
		<description lang="pl_PL">Wygaszacz ekranu wyświetlający cyfrowy zegar z datą, informacjami o aktualnie odtwarzanych mediach, o pogodzie, pokaz slajdów i kilkoma innymi opcjami.</description>
		<description lang="ru_RU">Заставка цифровых часов, с датой, с информацией о погоде, со слайд-шоу и с несколькими опциями.</description>
		<description lang="sr_RS">Чувар екрана дигитални сат са датумом, подацима о тренутној репродукцији, подацима о временској прогнози, репродукцијом слајдова слика и неколико опција.</description>
		<description lang="sr_RS@latin">Čuvar ekrana digitalni sat sa datumom, podacima o trenutnoj reprodukciji, podacima o vremenskoj prognozi, reprodukcijom slajdova slika i nekoliko opcija.</description>
		<description lang="tr_TR">Dijital saat ekran koruyucu, tarih ve saatin yanı sıra şimdi oynatılıyor bilgisi, hava durumu bilgisi, resim slayt gösterisi gibi çeşitli seçenekler sunar.</description>
		<description lang="zh_CN">数字时钟屏幕保护程序，带有日期、当前播放信息、天气信息、图片幻灯片和多个选项。</description>
		<disclaimer lang="da_DK">Ved fejl, anmodninger eller generelle spørgsmål, besøg tråden Pauseskærm med digital ur på Kodi-forummet.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="de_DE">Für Fehler, Wünsche oder allgemeine Fragen den Thread „Digital clock screensaver“ im Kodi-Forum besuchen.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="en_GB">For bugs, requests or general questions visit the Digital clock screensaver thread on the Kodi forum.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="en_NZ">For bugs, requests or general questions visit the Digital clock screensaver thread on the Kodi forum.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="es_ES">Para errores, peticiones o cuestiones generales visite el hilo Salvapantallas reloj digital en el foro de Kodi.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="fr_CA">Concernant les bogues ou pour des questions générales, visitez le fil « Digital clock screensaver » du forum de Kodi.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="fr_FR">Pour les bogues, demandes ou questions générales, merci de visiter le fil de discussion de l&apos;économiseur d&apos;écran horloge numérique, Digital clock screensaver, sur le forum Kodi.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="it_IT">Per bug, richieste o domande generali visita il thread del salvaschermo orologio digitale sul forum Kodi.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="lt_LT">Norėdami pranešti apie klaidą, pateikti prašymą ar tiesiog paklausti, aplankykite skaitmeninio laikrodžio ekrano užsklandos temą Kodi forume.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ms_MY">Jika ada pepijat, permintaan atau persoalan umum sila lawati bebenang Digital clock screensaver di dalam forum Kodi.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="pl_PL">Odwiedź dedykowany wygaszaczowi wątek na forum Kodi, aby zgłosić błędy, prośbę o funkcje albo zadać ogólne pytanie.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ru_RU">Для сообщений об ошибках, для пожеланий, для общих вопросов, посетите тему дополнения в форуме Kodi.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="sr_RS">За проблеме, захтеве или општа питања посетите Digital clock screensaver тему на Kodi форуму.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="sr_RS@latin">Za probleme, zahteve ili opšta pitanja posetite Digital clock screensaver temu na Kodi forumu.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="tr_TR">Hata bildirme, istek ve genel sorularınız için Kodi forumunda dijital saat ekran koruyucu başlığını ziyaret edebilirsiniz.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="zh_CN">有关 bug、请求或一般问题，请访问 Kodi 论坛上的数字时钟屏幕保护程序讨论贴。</disclaimer>
	</extension>
</addon>
