<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<addon id="service.subtitles.opensubtitles"
       name="OpenSubtitles.org"
       version="5.0.16"
       provider-name="amet, opensubtitles">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.subtitle.module"
             library="service.py" />
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary>OpenSubtitles</summary>
    <description lang="en">Search and download subtitles for movies and TV-Series from OpenSubtitles.org. Search in 75 languages, 4.000.000+ subtitles, daily updates.</description>
	<description lang="at">Pelis and Subtítulos TV en munches llingües, milenta de subtítulos traducíos y xubíos caldía. Descarga llibre dende la fonte, sofitu API, millones d'usuarios.</description>
	<description lang="br">Istitloù Filmoù ha TV e meur a yezh, miliadoù a istitloù troet hag uskarget bemdez. Pellgargadenn digoust diouzh ar vammenn, skoazell an API, millionoù a implijerien.</description>
	<description lang="ca">Subtítols de films i televisió en múltiples idiomes, milers de subtítols traduïts carregats diàriament. Descàrrega gratuïta des de la font, suport de l'API, amb milions d'usuaris.</description>
	<description lang="cs">Titulky k filmům a seriálům v mnoha jazycích, denně tisíce nahraných přeložených titulků. Stažení zadarmo přímo od zdroje, podpora API, milióny uživatelů.</description>
	<description lang="de">Film- und TV-Untertitel in vielen Sprachen, täglicher Upload von tausenden übersetzten Untertiteln. Freier Download von der Quelle, API-Unterstützung, Millionen Nutzer</description>
	<description lang="el">Ταινίες και Σειρές σε όλες τις γλώσσες, χιλιάδες μεταφρασμένοι υπότιτλοι ανεβαίνουν καθημερινά, κατεβάστε δωρεάν , υποστήριξη API από εκατομμύρια χρήστες</description>
	<description lang="eo">Filmaj kaj Televidaj subtekstoj en multaj lingvoj, miloj da tradukitaj subtekstoj ĉiutage alŝutataj. Senpaga elŝuto de fonto, API-subteno, miloj da uzantoj.</description>
	<description lang="es">Películas y Subtítulos en diversos idiomas, miles de subtítulos traducidos subidos diariamente. Descarge gratis, soporte API, millones de usuarios.</description>
	<description lang="et">Sadu Filmi ja TV Serjaalide subtiitrid erinevates keeltes laetakse üles igapäev. tasuta allalaadimine ja abi, rohkem kui miljon kasutajat.</description>
	<description lang="eu">Film eta Telebista azpitituluak hizkuntza anitzetan, milaka azpititulu itzuliak igotzen dira egunero. Doan jaitsi iturburutik, API sostengua, milioika erabiltzaile.</description>
	<description lang="fi">Tekstityksiä useilla kielillä elokuviin ja TV-Sarjoihin, tuhansia uusia tekstityksiä päivittäin, ilmainen lataus, API tuki, miljoonia käyttäjiä.</description>
	<description lang="fr">Les sous-titres de film et téléfilm en plusieurs langues, des milliers de sous-titres traduits tous les jours. Bénéficiez de téléchargements gratuits depuis la source, du support API, une d'une communauté de millions d'utilisateurs.</description>
	<description lang="hi">मूवी और टीवी उपशीर्षक कई भाषाओं में अनुवाद उपशीर्षक के हजारों दैनिक अपलोड की गई। मुफ्त डाउनलोड स्रोत से , एपीआई समर्थन, उपयोगकर्ताओं के लाखों लोगों की ।</description>
	<description lang="hr">Titlovi za filmove i TV na mnogim jezicima, tisuće prijevoda postavljenih svaki dan. Besplatno preuzimanje s izvora, podrška za API, milijuni korisnika.</description>
	<description lang="hu">Film és TV feliratok több nyelven, naponta több ezer lefordított felirat feltöltés. Ingyenes letöltés a forrástól, API támogatás, több millió felhasználó.</description>
	<description lang="id">Subjudul film dan serial TV dalam multibahasa, ribuan subjudul diterjemah dan diunggah setiap harinya. Pengunduhan gratis dari sumber, didukung fitur antarmuka pemrograman aplikasi, dan jutaan pengguna.</description>
	<description lang="is">Textar fyrir myndir og sjónvarpsþ. á mörgum tungumálum, þúsundir af þýddum textum upphlaðið daglega. Frítt niðurhal frá síðu, API stuðningur, milljónir notenda.</description>
	<description lang="it">Sottotitoli di Film e TV in più lingue,migliaia di sottotitoli tradotti caricati ogni giorno.Download gratuito,supporto API, milioni di utenti.</description>
	<description lang="ja">映画やテレビの字幕をさまざまな言語で。毎日数多くの翻訳字幕がアップロードされています。ソースを無料ダウンロード、API 対応、数百万を超えるユーザー。</description>
	<description lang="ka">სუბტიტრები ფილმებისა და ტვ-სთვის მრავალ ენაზე. ათასობიტ თარგმნილი სუბტიტრის ატვირთვა ყოველდღიურად. უდასო ჩამოტვირტვა წყაროდან, API მხარდაჭერა, მილიონობით მომხმარებელი</description>
	<description lang="km">អត្ថបទរឿងសម្រាប់ ខ្សែភាពយន្ត និងកម្មវិធីទូរទស្សន៍​ ជាភាសាជាច្រើន រួមនឹងអត្ថបទរឿងបកប្រែរាប់ពាន់​រឿង​ដែល​ត្រូវបាន​អ័ពឡូដជារៀងរាល់ថ្ងៃ។ ទាញយកដោយឥតគិតថ្លៃពីប្រភពដើម គាំទ្រ API និងមានអ្នកប្រើប្រាស់រាប់លាននាក់។ </description>
	<description lang="ko">Movie and TV Subtitles in multiple languages, thousands of translated subtitles uploaded daily. Free download from source, API support, millions of users.</description>
	<description lang="ms">Sarikata TV dan Movie dalam pelbagai bahasa, ribuan terjemahan sarikata dimuat-naik setiap hari.Muat-turun percuma dari sumber utama, sokongan API, jutaan pengguna.</description>
	<description lang="nl">Ondertitels voor films en tv-series in meerdere talen, dagelijks upload van duizenden vertaalde ondertitels. Gratis downloaden van de bron, API ondersteuning, miljoenen gebruikers.</description>
	<description lang="no">Undertekster for film og TV på mange språk, med tusener av nye oversettelser hver dag. Vi har gratis nedlasting av undertekster, API-support, og mange millioner brukere.</description>
	<description lang="pt-br">Milhares de legendas para filmes e seriados de TV, em vários idiomas, são traduzidas e enviadas diariamente. Download grátis, suporte API e milhões de usuários.</description>
	<description lang="pl">Napisy do filmów i seriali w wielu językach. Tysiące napisów dodawanych codziennie. Darmowe pobranie, miliony użytkowników.</description>
	<description lang="pt">Legendas de filmes e séries de TV em vários idiomas, milhares de legendas traduzidas e enviadas diariamente. Download grátis a partir da fonte, suporte API, milhões de utilizadores.</description>
	<description lang="ro">Subtitrari pentru filme in multe limbi, mii de subtitrari traduse si încărcate in fiecare zi. Descărca gratuit de la sursă, suport API, milioane de utilizatori.</description>
	<description lang="ru">Кино и ТВ субтитры на нескольких языках, тысячи переведенными субтитрами загружены ежедневно. Бесплатно скачать из исходных текстов, поддержка API, миллионы пользователей.</description>
	<description lang="sk">Titulky pre filmy a TV seriály, denne nahratých tisíce titulkov preložených vo viacerých jazykoch. Sťahuj zadarmo zo zdroja, podpora API, milióny používateľov.</description>
	<description lang="sl">Filmski in televizijski podnapisi v mnogo jezikih, na tisoče prevedenih podnapisov dnevno. Brezplačen prenos iz vira, podpora API, miljoni uporabnikov.</description>
	<description lang="sq">Titra filmash dhe serialesh në shumë gjuhë, mijëra titra të përkthyera që vendosen çdo ditë. Shkarko nga burimi, apo nga mbështetja e API-së, miliona përdorues.</description>
	<description lang="sr">Titlovi za filmove i TV na mnogim jezicima, hiljade prevoda okačenih svakodnevno. Besplatno skidanje sa izvora, podrška za API, milioni korisnika.</description>
	<description lang="sv">Filmer och Tv-undertexter med olika språk, tusentals översatta undertexter uppladdade dagligen. Gratis nerladdning från källor, API support, miljoner av användare.</description>
	<description lang="tr">Her gün eklenen, pek çok dildeki binlerce film ve dizi altyazısı. Kaynağından ücretsiz indirme, API desteği ve milyonlarca kullanıcı.</description>
	<description lang="uz">Film va TV Taglavhalari ko'p tillarda, minglab tarjima qilingan taglavhalar har kuni tizimga yuklanadi. Bepul resursdan yuklab oling, API qo'llaydi, millionlab foydalanuvchilar.</description>
	<description lang="zh">多语种的电影及剧集字幕，每日更新千余条翻译好的字幕。免费下载，提供API接口，已拥有上百万的用户。</description>
    <disclaimer>Users need to provide OpenSubtitles.org username and password in add-on configuration</disclaimer>                                               
	<news>
v5.0.16 (2016-11-26) by opensubtitles
- Changed descriptions, icons, fanart... (by opensubtitles)

v5.0.15 (2016-11-26) by amet
- disable anonymous login, users need to register on opensubtitles.org and login in addon settings.
	</news>
    <platform>all</platform>
	<language></language>
    <license>GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE. Version 2, June 1991</license>
    <forum>https://forum.opensubtitles.org/viewtopic.php?f=8&amp;t=15847</forum>
    <website>http://www.opensubtitles.org</website>
    <email>admin [at] opensubtitles {dot} org</email>                                               
	<assets>
	    <icon>resources/media/os_logo_512x512.png</icon>
	    <fanart>resources/media/os_fanart.jpg</fanart>    
		<screenshot>resources/media/screenshot_1.jpg</screenshot>
		<screenshot>resources/media/screenshot_2.jpg</screenshot>
		<screenshot>resources/media/screenshot_3.jpg</screenshot>				
	</assets>
    <source>https://github.com/opensubtitles/service.subtitles.opensubtitles</source>    
  </extension>
</addon>
