<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<addon id="script.videoextras" name="VideoExtras" version="2.0.1" provider-name="robwebset">
	<requires>
    	<import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.20.0"/>
		<import addon="script.module.simplejson" version="3.3.0"/>
  	</requires>
  	<extension point="xbmc.python.script" library="default.py" />
	<extension point="xbmc.service" library="service.py" start="login">
		<provides>executable</provides>
	</extension>
	<extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="plugin.py">
		<provides>video</provides>
	</extension>
	<extension point="kodi.context.item" library="contextmenu.py">
		<item>
			<label>32028</label>
			<visible>!IsEmpty(Window(videos).Property("VideoExtrasShowContextMenu")) + [Container.Content(movies) | Container.Content(episodes) | Container.Content(tvshows) | Container.Content(seasons) | Container.Content(musicvideos)]</visible>
		</item>
	</extension>
  	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    	<summary lang="ca">Afegeix vídeos extres a les teves pel·lícules i sèries de televisió.</summary>
    	<summary lang="cs">Přidej Video bonusy k Filmům a TV seriím</summary>
    	<summary lang="de">Video Extras zu den Filmen und TV-Sendungen in Ihrer Sammlung hinzufügen</summary>
    	<summary lang="el">Προσθήκη DVD Extras στις Ταινίες και τις Τηλεοπτικές σας Σειρές.</summary>
    	<summary lang="en">Add Video Extras to your Movies and TV shows.</summary>
    	<summary lang="en_NZ">Add Video Extras to your Movies and TV shows.</summary>
    	<summary lang="en_US">Add Video Extras to your Movies and TV shows.</summary>
    	<summary lang="es">Añadir extras de vídeo para sus películas y programas de televisión.</summary>
    	<summary lang="fr">Ajouter des bonus vidéo à vos films et séries TV.</summary>
    	<summary lang="fr_CA">Ajouter des bonus vidéos à vos films et séries télé.</summary>
    	<summary lang="gl">Engadir Extras de Vídeos aos seus Filmes e Series de TV.</summary>
    	<summary lang="he">הוסף ספיישלים (Video Extras) לסרטים ולסדרות שלך.</summary>
    	<summary lang="hr">Dodajte video dodatke vašim filmovima i TV emisijama.</summary>
    	<summary lang="hu">Videó Extrák a Filmekhez és Sorozatokhoz</summary>
    	<summary lang="is">Bætir Video Extras við Kvikmyndir og Sjónvarpsþætti</summary>
    	<summary lang="it">Aggiungi i Video Extra ai tuoi Video e Serie tv</summary>
    	<summary lang="ko">영화와 TV 쇼 라이브러리에 부가영상 추가</summary>
    	<summary lang="lt">Pridėkite video priedus filmams ir TV laidoms.</summary>
    	<summary lang="nl">Voeg Video extra`s toe aan jou Films en TV series.</summary>
    	<summary lang="pl">Wparcie dodatkowych materiałów dla filmów i seriali telewizyjnych.</summary>
    	<summary lang="pt">Adicionar Extras de Vídeo aos seus Filmes e Séries TV</summary>
    	<summary lang="pt_BR">Adiciona extras de vídeos em filmes e seriados.</summary>
    	<summary lang="sv">Lägg till Video Extras till dina filmer och TV-program</summary>
    	<description lang="ca">Proporciona una manera d'afegir vídeo extres a la seva biblioteca de vídeo. Mira el wiki per instruccions d'instal·lació.</description>
    	<description lang="cs">Poskytuje způsob jak přidat Bonusy do vaší video knihovny. Instrukce pro nastavení viz. wiki.</description>
    	<description lang="de">Bietet eine Möglichkeit, um Videoextras zu Ihrer Videobibliothek hinzuzufügen. Schauen Sie ins Wiki für Installationsanweisungen.</description>
    	<description lang="el">Σας παρέχει έναν τρόπο να προσθέσετε DVD Extras στη Συλλογή σας. Ελέγξτε τον ιστότοπο του wiki για οδηγίες εγκατάστασης.</description>
    	<description lang="en">Provides a way to add Video Extras to your Video library. Look at the wiki for setup instructions.</description>
    	<description lang="en_NZ">Provides a way to add Video Extras to your Video library. Look at the wiki for setup instructions.</description>
    	<description lang="en_US">Provides a way to add Video Extras to your Video library. Look at the wiki for setup instructions.</description>
    	<description lang="es">Proporciona una manera de añadir extras de vídeos a su biblioteca. Mira el wiki para instrucciones de instalación.</description>
    	<description lang="fr">Fournit une solution pour ajouter des bonus vidéo à votre vidéothèque. Cherchez dans le Wiki les instructions de paramétrage.</description>
    	<description lang="fr_CA">Offre une façon d'ajouter des bonus vidéos à votre vidéothèque. Consulter le wiki pour des instructions de configuration.</description>
    	<description lang="gl">Prové dun camiño para engadir Extras á sea biblioteca de Vídeos. Ver na wiki para instruccións da configuración.</description>
    	<description lang="he">מספק אפשרות להוסיף ספיישלים (Video Extras) לספריית הוידאו שלך. פנה לוויקי להוראות התקנה.</description>
    	<description lang="hr">Pruža vam način dodavanja video dodataka u vašu videoteku. Potražite na wiki stranicama informacije za podešavanje.</description>
    	<description lang="hu">Biztosítja a lehetőséget hogy Extrákat adjon hozzá a Videó Médiatárához. Nézze meg a wiki-t a telepítés beállításához.</description>
    	<description lang="is">Gerir kleyft að bæta við Video Extras við myndasöfnin þín. Skoðaðu wiki til að sjá hvernig þetta er sett upp. Video Extras heldur utan um smámyndir og Fanart og fl og sér á skipulegan hátt um að geyma og halda utan um það.</description>
    	<description lang="it">Provvede un modo per aggiungere Video Extra alla tua biblioteca Video. Consulta il wiki per le istruzioni di configurazione..</description>
    	<description lang="ko">비디오 라이브러리에 부가영상(보너스 영상, 셔플, 다른 버전 등)을 추가할 수 있게 합니다. 설치 방법은 Kodi 위키를 참조하세요.</description>
    	<description lang="lt">Suteikia būdą pridėti video priedus į vaizdo biblioteką. Nustatymo instrukcijas galite rasti vikio puslapyje.</description>
    	<description lang="nl">Biedt een manier om Video extra`s toe te voegen aan jou videobibliotheek. Kijk op de wiki voor instellingsinstructies.</description>
    	<description lang="pl">Umożliwia dodanie dodatkowych materiałów wideo do biblioteki wideo. Zapoznaj się z informacjami na stronach Wiki w celu poprawnej konfiguracji. </description>
    	<description lang="pt">Permite adicionar extras de vídeo à sua Biblioteca de Vídeos. Leia o wiki para mais instruções de configuração.</description>
    	<description lang="pt_BR">Prove um caminho para vídeo extras via info de vídeo. Ver o wiki para instruções de configuração.</description>
    	<description lang="sv">Tillhandahåller ett sätt att lägga till Video Extras till ditt filmbibliotek. Se wiki för inställningsanvisningar.</description>
    	<disclaimer lang="cs">Tvůrci skinů: http://wiki.kodi.tv/index.php?title=Add-on:VideoExtras</disclaimer>
    	<disclaimer lang="de">Skin-Ersteller, bitte schaut für Informationen über die Integration in euren Skin im Wiki:&#10;http://wiki.kodi.tv/index.php?title=Add-on:VideoExtras</disclaimer>
    	<disclaimer lang="el">Skinners, ελέγξτε τον ιστότοπο για πληροφορίες σχετικά με την ενσωμάτωση στο κέλυφός σας: http://wiki.kodi.tv/index.php?title=Add-on:VideoExtras</disclaimer>
    	<disclaimer lang="en">Skinners, please see the wiki to know how to integrate it in your skin: http://wiki.kodi.tv/index.php?title=Add-on:VideoExtras</disclaimer>
    	<disclaimer lang="en_US">Skinners, please see the wiki to know how to integrate it in your skin: http://wiki.kodi.tv/index.php?title=Add-on:VideoExtras</disclaimer>
    	<disclaimer lang="es">Desarrolladores, por favor ver el Wiki para saber como integrarlo en tu Skin&#10;http://wiki.kodi.tv/index.php?title=Add-on:VideoExtras</disclaimer>
    	<disclaimer lang="fr">Skinneurs, lisez le Wiki afin d'obtenir les informations pour l'intégrer à votre skin: : http://wiki.kodi.tv/index.php?title=Add-on:VideoExtras</disclaimer>
    	<disclaimer lang="fr_CA">Habilleurs, consultez le wiki pour savoir comment l'intégrer à votre habillage : http://wiki.kodi.tv/index.php?title=Add-on:VideoExtras</disclaimer>
    	<disclaimer lang="gl">Autores de temas, por favor vexan a wiki para saber como integralo no seu tema:&#10;http://wiki.kodi.tv/index.php?title=Add-on:VideoExtras</disclaimer>
    	<disclaimer lang="ko">스킨 제작자 여러분, 스킨에 통합하는 방법은 위키를 참조하기 바랍니다: http://wiki.kodi.tv/index.php?title=Add-on:VideoExtras</disclaimer>
    	<disclaimer lang="lt">Teminių išvaizdų kūrėjai, instrukcijas kaip integruoti šį priedą į jūsų teminę išvaizdą rasite vikio puslapyje: http://wiki.kodi.tv/index.php?title=Add-on:VideoExtras</disclaimer>
    	<disclaimer lang="nl">Skinners, bekijk de wikie om te weten hoe je heet moet integreren in jouw skin: http://wiki.kodi.tv/index.php?title=Add-on:VideoExtras</disclaimer>
    	<disclaimer lang="pl">Twórcy skór powinni zapoznać się z informacjami na stronach Wiki, aby dowiedzieć więcej o integracji z dodatkiem: http://wiki.kodi.tv/index.php?title=Add-on:VideoExtras</disclaimer>
    	<disclaimer lang="pt">Os autores dos temas deverão consultar o wiki para saberem como integrar este add-on no tema: http://wiki.kodi.tv/index.php?title=Add-on:VideoExtras</disclaimer>
    	<disclaimer lang="pt_BR">Skinners, por favor veja o wiki para saber como integrar em sua skin:&#10;http://wiki.kodi.tv/index.php?title=Add-on:VideoExtras</disclaimer>
    	<disclaimer lang="sv">Skaltillverkare, använd wikin för att se hur du kan integrera det i ditt skal:&#10;http://wiki.kodi.tv/index.php?title=Add-on:VideoExtras</disclaimer>
    	<language></language>
    	<platform>all</platform>
    	<license>GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE. Version 2, June 1991</license>
    	<forum>http://forum.kodi.tv/showthread.php?tid=214289</forum>
    	<source>https://github.com/robwebset/script.videoextras</source>
  </extension>
</addon>
